<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20240924</CreaDate><CreaTime>14271200</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20240924</ModDate><ModTime>14353200</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><idPurp>This folder contains shapefiles representing faults, topographic sections, and surface hydrogeological units within the Mexico Basin. The dataset includes detailed information on the surface lengths and orientations of faults and sections, as well as the spatial distribution of hydrogeological units across the basin's surface.
</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Surface folder comprises a collection of shapefiles designed to represent key geological and hydrogeological features within the Mexico Basin. It includes the following components:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;1. **Faults**: Shapefile representing the location and surface extent of major geological faults in the basin. Each fault includes attributes such as surface length and orientation, providing important data for structural geology and tectonic analysis.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;2. **Sections**: Shapefile that contain topographic cross-sections across the basin. Each section records surface length and orientation attributes.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;3. **Surface Hydrogeological Units**: Shapefiles depicting the distribution of hydrogeological units at the surface, offering insights into the spatial arrangement of relevant units. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;This dataset is valuable for geospatial analysis, hydrogeological modeling, and geological research. The data can be used in various GIS platforms to support the study of surface geology, fault dynamics, and hydrogeological characteristics in the region.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>This dataset was created by Juan Camilo Montaño Caro as part of a comprehensive study of the Mexico Basin's hydrogeological and geological characteristics. The shapefiles were generated using GIS tools and data sources from topographic and geological surveys.
</idCredit><idCitation><resTitle>Plan view of hydrological  units, faults, and  topographic sections in surface.</resTitle></idCitation><searchKeys><keyword>Faults</keyword><keyword>Topographic Sections</keyword><keyword>Surface Lengths</keyword><keyword>Orientations</keyword><keyword>Hydrogeological Units</keyword><keyword>Mexico Basin</keyword><keyword>Surface Geology</keyword><keyword>GIS</keyword><keyword>Geospatial Analysis</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv></metadata>
