<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20240924</CreaDate><CreaTime>14362200</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20240924</ModDate><ModTime>14475100</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><idPurp>The Hydrogeological_Units folder is divided into two subfolders: one containing line shapefiles for hydrogeological units and faults, and the other containing polygon shapefiles for hydrogeological units. Each shapefile is linked to specific topographic sections within the Mexico Basin, offering detailed geospatial data for hydrogeological studies.
</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Hydrogeological_Units folder contains geospatial data organized into two subfolders, each designed to represent hydrogeological features in the Mexico Basin:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;1. **Lineal Subfolder**: This subfolder includes line shapefiles representing the boundaries of hydrogeological units and major faults across the basin. Each file corresponds to specific topographic sections, providing valuable data for understanding the structure and connectivity of hydrogeological units in relation to geological faults.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;2. **Polygon Subfolder**: The polygon shapefiles in this subfolder depict the spatial extent of hydrogeological units within the basin. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Each shapefile in both subfolders is associated with specific topographic sections, enabling comprehensive analysis of hydrogeological conditions across the basin’s diverse terrain. The data is suitable for use in GIS platforms to support hydrogeological modeling, groundwater resource assessments, and geological investigations.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>This dataset was produced by Juan Camilo Montaño Caro as part of the hydrogeological study of the Mexico Basin. The data was compiled using GIS tools and topographic survey data. These shapefiles provide a foundation for understanding the distribution and structure of hydrogeological units and faults within the basin.
</idCredit><searchKeys><keyword>Hydrogeological Units</keyword><keyword>Faults</keyword><keyword>Line Shapefiles</keyword><keyword>Polygon Shapefiles</keyword><keyword>Mexico Basin</keyword><keyword>Topographic Sections</keyword><keyword>Geospatial Analysis</keyword><keyword>GIS</keyword><keyword>Hydrogeology</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv></metadata>
