<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20240924</CreaDate><CreaTime>14215400</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20240924</ModDate><ModTime>14260200</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><idPurp>This dataset contains topographic sections generated for the Mexico Basin, providing elevation profiles across various transects. These sections are intended for use in hydrogeological and geospatial analysis, offering insights into terrain variations and the overall topography of the region.
</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The topographic sections in this dataset were derived from a Digital Elevation Model (DEM) and are aimed at studying the Mexico Basin's terrain characteristics . The sections represent cross-sectional profiles that capture the variation in elevation across the basin at specific transects. These sections can be used for hydrogeological modeling, geospatial analysis, and terrain assessment. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Each section was generated with precision to ensure the accurate representation of the topographic features, providing valuable data for understanding the geological and hydrological dynamics of the region. The data can be integrated into various GIS platforms for further spatial analysis and modeling.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN /&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>This dataset was produced by Juan Camilo Montaño Caro as part of a project on the hydrogeological modeling of the Mexico Basin. The analysis was conducted using open-source tools and geographic information systems (GIS), with data derived from DEMs and other geospatial sources.
</idCredit><idCitation><resTitle>Topographic Sections</resTitle></idCitation><searchKeys><keyword>Topographic Sections</keyword><keyword>Mexico Basin</keyword><keyword>Elevation Profiles</keyword><keyword>Hydrogeology</keyword><keyword>GIS</keyword><keyword>DEM</keyword><keyword>Geospatial Analysis</keyword><keyword>Terrain</keyword><keyword>Contour Lines</keyword><keyword>Cross-Sections</keyword></searchKeys></dataIdInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv></metadata>
